<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>US Military on Cletus's Blog</title><link>/cletus/tags/us-military/</link><description>Cletus's Blog (US Military)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/cletus/tags/us-military/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Military - 2025-03-03</title><link>/cletus/posts/us-military/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cletus/posts/us-military/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="16-af-newsroom" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#16-af-newsroom">
##
&lt;/a>
16 AF Newsroom
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/4062792/16th-air-force-member-stays-resilient-through-kidney-disease/">16th Air Force member stays resilient through kidney disease&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/4026872/526th-intelligence-squadron-creates-midnite-apex-increasing-combat-readiness-fo/">526th Intelligence Squadron creates MIDNITE APEX, increasing combat readiness for peer conflict&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/4015496/363d-isr-wing-recognized-with-meritorious-unit-award-from-june-1-2023-to-may-31/">363d ISR Wing recognized with Meritorious Unit Award from June 1, 2023 to May 31, 2024&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3999424/aftac-hosts-scouts-for-merit-badge-event/">AFTAC hosts scouts for merit badge event&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3998301/comacc-command-chief-immerse-into-aftac-mission/">COMACC, Command Chief immerse into AFTAC mission&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3992107/16th-air-force-strengthens-strategic-partnerships-increases-interoperability-in/">16th Air Force strengthens strategic partnerships, increases interoperability in NATOâs largest cyber defense exercise&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3985460/16th-air-force-continues-poland-cyber-command-partnership-with-first-ever-malwa/">16th Air Force continues Poland Cyber Command partnership with first-ever malware attack exercise&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3925601/defense-attach-group-visits-16th-air-force-prepares-for-integrated-deterrence/">Defense Attaché group visits 16th Air Force, prepares for integrated deterrence&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3928155/growing-cyber-threats-prompt-philippine-armys-1st-16th-af-visit/">Growing Cyber threats prompt Philippine Armyâs 1st 16th AF visit&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Article-Display/Article/3926621/commentary-my-first-time-riding-the-memorial-to-memorial-cycling-event/">Commentary: My first time riding the Memorial to Memorial Cycling Event&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/283418/fact_sheet_army_food_program">FACT SHEET: Army Food Program&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/283111/fort_liberty_is_renamed_fort_bragg_effective_immediately">Fort Liberty is renamed Fort Bragg, effective immediately&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282965/army_prepares_to_celebrate_its_250th_birthday_on_june_14_2025">Army prepares to celebrate its 250th birthday on June 14, 2025&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282896/army_breaks_ground_on_state_of_the_art_6_8_mm_ammunition_production_facility">Army breaks ground on state-of-the-art 6.8 mm ammunition production facility&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282782/u_s_army_south_leads_joint_task_force_in_support_of_illegal_alien_holding_operation_in_guantanamo_bay">U.S. Army South leads joint task force in support of illegal alien holding operation in Guantanamo Bay&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282772/army_identifies_third_soldier_involved_in_helicopter_crash">Army identifies Third Soldier involved in Helicopter Crash&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282769/fact_sheet_dca_crash_army_aviation_operational_insights_in_the_ncr">FACT SHEET: DCA Crash-Army aviation operational insights in the NCR&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282768/the_department_of_army_identifies_two_of_three_army_soldiers_involved_in_helicopter_crash">The Department of Army identifies two of three Army Soldiers involved in Helicopter Crash&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282760/recovery_underway_for_u_s_army_helicopter_crash">Recovery Underway for U.S. Army Helicopter Crash&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282349/president_to_honor_seven_soldiers_with_nations_top_valor_award">President to honor seven Soldiers with nation’s top valor award&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282104/army_considers_microreactors_to_increase_installation_readiness_and_resilience">Army considers microreactors to increase installation readiness and resilience&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/282100/honoring_excellence_2024_army_acquisition_executive_awards_celebrate_acquisition_innovators">Honoring excellence: 2024 Army Acquisition Executive Awards celebrate acquisition innovators&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/281829/u_s_army_releases_americas_army_2024_year_in_review">U.S. Army releases ‘America’s Army: 2024 Year in Review’&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/281767/during_a_pentagon_ceremony_the_secretary_of_the_army_appoints_five_new_civilian_aides">During a Pentagon ceremony the Secretary of the Army appoints five new civilian aides&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/281378/army_releases_fiscal_year_2024_annual_financial_report_and_audit_results">Army releases Fiscal Year 2024 Annual Financial Report and audit results&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/281247/u_s_army_awards_contract_for_domestic_tnt_production">U.S. Army awards contract for domestic TNT production&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/280500/army_launches_pilot_to_explore_generative_ai_for_acquisition_activities">Army launches pilot to explore generative AI for acquisition activities&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/280537/army_to_pilot_secure_cloud_environment_for_small_businesses_in_the_defense_industrial_base">Army to pilot secure, cloud environment for small businesses in the defense industrial base&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/280028/army_exceeds_fy_2024_active_duty_recruiting_goals">Army exceeds FY 2024 active duty recruiting goals&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/279956/2024_class_of_the_army_acquisition_hall_of_fame_announced">2024 class of the Army Acquisition Hall of Fame announced&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/279907/ukrainian_president_zelenskyy_praises_scranton_dod_for_role_supporting_ukraine">Ukrainian President Zelenskyy praises Scranton, DOD for role supporting Ukraine&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/279836/in_letter_to_congress_army_secretary_outlines_continuing_resolution_concerns">In letter to Congress, Army Secretary outlines Continuing Resolution concerns&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/279124/army_selects_sierra_nevada_corporation_as_lead_system_integrator_for_its_high_accuracy_detection_and_exploitation_system">Army selects Sierra Nevada Corporation as lead system integrator for its High Accuracy Detection and Exploitation System&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/278824/dod_announces_launch_of_online_housing_feedback_system">DOD announces launch of online Housing Feedback System&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/article/278708/army_announces_groundbreaking_for_cost_effective_sustainable_materials_barracks_at_jblm">Army announces groundbreaking for cost-effective sustainable materials barracks at JBLM&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Press-Office/Press-Briefings">Subject specific information for the media&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Press-Office/Press-Releases">Events or announcements of note for the media&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/Press-Office/Testimony">HASC, SASC and Congressional testimony&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.16af.af.mil/Newsroom/">United States NavyChief of InformationAttn: US Navy1200 Navy PentagonWashington DC 20350-1200&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="marines-news-releases" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#marines-news-releases">
##
&lt;/a>
Marines News Releases
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/4052117/marine-corps-passes-fy24-financial-audit/">02/04/2025Marine Corps Passes FY24 Financial AuditFor the second year in a row, independent auditors verified that the Marine Corps’ financial records are materially accurate, complete, and compliant with federal regulations and issued an unmodified opinion for Fiscal Year 2024.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/4047771/deputy-commandant-for-aviation-unveils-2025-aviation-plan-reinforcing-future-re/">02/03/2025Deputy Commandant for Aviation Unveils 2025 Aviation Plan, Reinforcing Future Readiness and Technological IntegrationHeadquarters Marine Corps Aviation released the 2025 Marine Corps Aviation Plan, outlining a strategic framework that balances responding to today’s crises with modernizing Marine Aviation to ensure the Corps is prepared for tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s fight. TheRead More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/4014125/death-of-general-thomas-r-morgan-21st-assistant-commandant-of-the-marine-corps/">12/20/2024Death of General Thomas R. Morgan, 21st Assistant Commandant of the Marine CorpsThe Marine Corps announces the passing of the 21st Assistant Commandant of the Marine Corps, General Thomas R. Morgan on December 6, 2024.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/4012676/marine-corps-releases-talent-management-update-remains-committed-to-empowering/">12/19/2024Marine Corps releases Talent Management Update, remains committed to empowering Marines while enhancing lethalityThe Marine Corps released the latest Talent Management update in support of Force Design, highlighting the continuous efforts to modernize and innovate its talent management systems, enhancing readiness and empowering Marines to thrive in a dynamic operational environment. Building on the foundation set by Talent Management 2030 and the Talent Management Campaign Plan 2023-2025, Manpower and Reserve Affairs (M&amp;amp;RA) achieved significant milestones in retaining, developing, and optimizing the force.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/4002316/usmcmod-joint-statement-commencement-of-force-flow/">12/14/2024USMC/MOD Joint Statement - Commencement of Force FlowA small detachment of approximately 100 logistics support Marines from III Marine Expeditionary Force (MEF) has started to relocate from Okinawa to Guam in line with the Joint Statement of the Security Consultative Committee (“2+2”) on July 28, 2024.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/3913938/marine-corps-crushes-fiscal-year-2024-end-strength-with-historic-retention-recr/">09/23/2024Marine Corps crushes fiscal year 2024 end strength with historic retention, recruiting successThe Marine Corps achieved historic first-term reenlistment numbers and exceeded its retention goal for Fiscal Year 2024 in a competitive and challenging environment. Engaged leaders across the Marine Corps retained the most qualified Marines at levels not seen in over a decade. Additionally, these efforts contributed to the Marine Corps exceeding its authorized end strength requirement, which is a summation of recruiting and retention efforts.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/3867626/secnav-del-toro-reflects-on-three-years-in-office-at-the-future-warfighting-sym/">08/08/2024SECNAV Del Toro Reflects on Three Years in Office at the Future Warfighting SymposiumSecretary of the Navy Carlos Del Toro delivered remarks at the Future Warfighting Symposium at the Naval War College in Newport, R.I., Aug. 8. Secretary Del Toro addressed new Naval War College (NWC) students, faculty, and staff on the eve of his third anniversary in office.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/3849706/marine-barracks-washington-to-host-enlisted-led-evening-parade/">07/24/2024MARINE BARRACKS WASHINGTON TO HOST ENLISTED-LED EVENING PARADEMarine Barracks Washington will host an enlisted-led Evening Parade at Marine Barracks Washington, D.C., this Friday, July 26 at 8:45 pm.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/3816553/marine-corps-launches-barracks-digital-maintenance-request-system-service-wide/">06/25/2024Marine Corps launches Barracks Digital Maintenance Request System Service-WideThe Marine Corps launched and has fully implemented QSRMax, which is the service’s main effort to upgrade its maintenance request system from analog to digital.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marines.mil/News/Press-Releases/Press-Release-Display/Article/3804646/cmc-signs-the-first-training-and-education-annual-report-on-force-design/">06/12/2024CMC Signs the First Training and Education Annual Report on Force DesignU.S. Marine Corps Commandant General Eric M. Smith has signed the U.S. Marine Corps Training and Education Annual Report (TEAR), June, 12, 2024. Published and distributed by Commanding General U.S. Marine Corps Training and Education Command (TECOM) Lieutenant General Kevin M. Iiams, the TEAR is the first annual report since the publishing of Training and Education 2030 (TE2030) by General David H. Berger, the 38th Commandant of the Marine Corps. The 14-page document outlines how CG TECOM has organized, progressed, and accomplished the 37 Force Design directed actions from TE2030.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="marforcyber-news" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#marforcyber-news">
##
&lt;/a>
MarForCyber News
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/3109116/the-marine-corps-is-stepping-up-its-efforts-to-turn-its-network-into-a-weapon/">Marines with Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command - Marines with Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command pose for photos in cyber operations room at Lasswell Hall aboard Fort Meade, Maryland, Feb. 5, 2020. MARFORCYBER Marines conduct offensive and defensive cyber operations in support of United States Cyber Command and operate, secure and defend the Marine Corps Enterprise Network. This image is a photo illustration.The Marine Corps is Stepping Up its Efforts to Turn its Network into a WeaponWhen the United States must rapidly respond to crisis, it sends the U.S. Marine Corps. Organized in a self-sufficient unit, a Marine Air Ground Task Force (MAGTF) brings together the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; infantry, armored, artillery, air, command, and logistics power to conduct highly-coordinated amphibious operations and landings abroad.These operationsRead More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2946604/marine-corps-enhances-its-cyber-cecurity-posture-by-activating-3d-network-batta/">Marine Corps Enhances its Cyber Cecurity Posture by Activating 3d Network BattalionThe Marine Corps is modernizing how it commands and controls its enterprise network.  A dedicated group will now empower the Corps’ ability to prevent and counter adversarial cyber-attacks and minimize network disruptions and outages.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2829653/marine-corps-activates-newest-cyber-defense-unit-to-secure-defend-reserve-force/">MARFORCYBER, MARFORRES, NETWORK, NETACT-RES, MFR, MCCOG - Col. Thomas Cleaver (left), commanding officer, Marine Corps Cyberspace Operations Group (MCCOG), Marine Forces Cyber Command (MARFORCYBER), takes charge of the formations of U.S. Marines and civilians during the Network Activity Reserve (NetAct-Res) activation ceremony at Marine Corps Support Facility New Orleans, Nov. 1, 2021.Marine Corps Activates Newest Cyber Defense Unit to Secure, Defend Reserve Force in CyberspaceThe Marine Corps has activated a new unit of cyber warriors in New Orleans to combat the ever-increasing threats in cyberspace in an effort to unify all cyber operations across the Corps. Unbeknownst to many, adversaries are disregarding traditional boundaries in attempts to disrupt and degrade communications, as well as, steal critical defense information on a daily basis. This unit is responsible for hardening, defending, and countering those threats for the Reserve Component spread across the United States at 158 Home Training Centers.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2333386/marine-corps-activates-network-activity-ncr-to-provide-unity-of-command-and-eff/">1st Network Activity - National Capital Region - Col. Edward J. Debish, the commanding officer of Marine Corps Cyberspace Operations Group speaks to Marines and civilians who are part of the new Network Activity - National Capital Region (NCR) during an activation ceremony at Marine Corps Base Quantico, Virginia, Aug. 31, 2020. Debish said “what this does for the Marine Corps, the big bang for our buck, is it provides unity of command and unity of effort.” The network provides robust, seamless, and secure end‐to‐end communications for all Marines; from the supporting establishment to forward-deployed forces.Marine Corps Activates Network Activity - NCR to Provide Unity of Command and Effort to the Enterprise NetworkThe Marine Corps is modernizing how it commands and controls its enterprise network. Now a dedicated group will upgrade the Corps’ ability to prevent and counter adversarial cyber-attacks and minimize network disruptions and outages.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2333524/future-cyberspace-operators-20-interns-take-up-cyberwarfare-summer-internship/">Midshipmen pose for a photo with David Luber, Executive Director, United States Cyber Command, at DreamPort in Columbia, Md., August 14. - Midshipmen pose for a photo with David Luber, Executive Director, United States Cyber Command, at DreamPort in Columbia, Md., August 14.Future Cyberspace Operators: 20 Interns Take Up Cyberwarfare Summer InternshipThe Marines are looking for the best and brightest minds to lead cyberspace operators in defense of the Nation. Nineteen U.S. Naval Academy Midshipmen and one Marine sergeant with the Marine Corps Enlisted Commissioning Education Program from The Citadel joined Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command for a summer internship at Fort George G. Meade, Maryland. The interns, hosted in two waves to mitigate the spread of COVID-19, were divided into small teams and embedded with seven of MARFORCYBER’s cyber mission force teams from 22 June to 14 August&amp;hellip;Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2228496/marine-corps-activates-new-battalion-to-fight-in-cyberspace/">U.S. Marines assigned to 1st Network Battalion, Marine Corps Cyberspace Operations Group, stand in formation during the battalion transfer of authority at Marine Corps Base Camp Pendleton, California, June 4, 2020. 1st Network Bn., the first of six new Marine Corps network units, was created to improve oversight, command, and control of the Marine Corps enterprise network while managing building and local area networks around base. (U.S. Marine Corps photo by Staff Sgt. Donald Holbert) - U.S. Marines assigned to 1st Network Battalion, Marine Corps Cyberspace Operations Group, stand in formation during the battalion transfer of authority at Marine Corps Base Camp Pendleton, California, June 4, 2020. 1st Network Bn., the first of six new Marine Corps network units, was created to improve oversight, command, and control of the Marine Corps enterprise network while managing building and local area networks around base. (U.S. Marine Corps photo by Staff Sgt. Donald Holbert)Marine Corps Activates New Battalion to Fight in CyberspaceAn impactful change to Marine Corps cyberspace and information technology modernization occurred on June 4, 2020, aboard Marine Corps Base Camp Pendleton, California, with the activation of 1st Network Battalion, which marked the beginning of the Marine Corps Enterprise Network (MCEN) Command and Control (C2) modernization implementation plan.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2207910/innovating-with-virtual-recruiting/">Marines attending the Gamerjibe virtual career fair on May 20, 2020 occupy the Marine Corps booth. The fair provided Students interested in technological careers the opportunity to connect virtually and free of charge using an immersive and interactive experience. - Marines attending the Gamerjibe virtual career fair on May 20, 2020 occupy the Marine Corps booth. The fair provided Students interested in technological careers the opportunity to connect virtually and free of charge using an immersive and interactive experience.Innovating with Virtual RecruitingRecruiters with the 8th Marine Corps District attended their first online virtual career fair hosted by Gamerjibe on May 20, 2020. Also attending the fair were Marines with Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command and Marine Corps Tactical Systems Support Activity. The online event, which was free and open to the public, helped Marine recruiters educate and inform potential candidates in attendance while simultaneously engaging with other entrepreneurs and tech businesses in attendance, all while from the safety of home. Attendees could voice, video and text chat with Marines while exploring the virtual booth for more information on technical career opportunities with the Marine Corps.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2194900/nathan-vanderhayden-from-marine-to-businessman/">Marine Corps veteran Staff Sergeant Nathanial Vanderhayden, formerly a Marine Corps cyber operator, takes a group photo with old friends, after receiving the Meritorious Service Medal at a dinner February 18th. - Marine Corps veteran Staff Sergeant Nathanial Vanderhayden, formerly a Marine Corps cyber operator, takes a group photo with old friends, after receiving the Meritorious Service Medal at a dinner February 18th. Major General Matthew Glavy, and Sgt. Maj. Dan Krause, the commanding general and sergeant major of Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command, awarded Nate with the Meritorious Service Medal for the superior performance of his duties. (U.S. Marine Corps photo by Lance Cpl. Garrett Gillespie)Nathan Vanderhayden | From Marine to BusinessmanMarine Corps veteran Nathanial Vanderhayden, formerly a Marine Corps cyber operator, received the Meritorious Service Medal at a dinner on February 18th.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2119187/marforcyber-hosts-digital-relief-and-appointment-ceremony-bids-sgt-maj-krause-f/">Maj. Gen. Matthew G. Glavy, Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command and Joint Task Force Ares commander, presides over a relief and appointment ceremony in Lasswell Hall, Fort Meade, Maryland, Mar. 19, 2020. During the ceremony, Sgt. Maj. Daniel L. Krause relinquished his duties as the sergeant major of MARFORCYBER while Sgt. Maj. Jay D. Williamson was appointed to fill the role. (Department of Defense photo by Joseph Wilbanks) - Maj. Gen. Matthew G. Glavy, Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command and Joint Task Force Ares commander, presides over a relief and appointment ceremony in Lasswell Hall, Fort Meade, Maryland, Mar. 19, 2020. During the ceremony, Sgt. Maj. Daniel L. Krause relinquished his duties as the sergeant major of MARFORCYBER while Sgt. Maj. Jay D. Williamson was appointed to fill the role. (Department of Defense photo by Joseph Wilbanks)MARFORCYBER Hosts Digital Relief and Appointment Ceremony: Bids Sgt. Maj. Krause Farewell, Welcomes Sgt. Maj. Williamson Through Video ConferenceFORT GEORGE G. MEADE, Md. – Sgt. Maj. Daniel L. Krause relinquished his duties as the sergeant major of Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command during a unique ceremony on Fort George G. Meade, Maryland, March 18.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.marforcyber.marines.mil/News/Article/Article/2088397/commandant-of-the-marine-corps-returns-to-marforcyber-hq-with-chief-of-naval-op/">Senior leaders visit Lasswell Hall - Maj. Gen. Mathew G. Glavy, commander of Marine Corps Forces Cyberspace Command and Joint Task Force Ares, welcomes Adm. Mike Gilday, 32nd Chief of Naval Operations and Gen. David H. Berger, 38th Commandant of the Marine Corps, to Lasswell Hall February 18, 2020. The senior leaders discussed current and future cyberspace operations conducted from the Joint Mission Operations Center Maryland. MARFORCYBER Marines conduct offensive and defensive cyber operations in support of United States Cyber Command and operate, secure and defend the Marine Corps Enterprise Network.Commandant of the Marine Corps Returns to MARFORCYBER HQ with Chief of Naval OperationsThe top-ranking officers from the Navy and Marine Corps, Adm. Mike Gilday, 32nd Chief of Naval Operations and Gen. David H. Berger, the 38th Commandant of the Marine Corps, visited Fort Meade, Maryland February 18, 2020. The two heads of the naval services toured Lasswell Hall and participated in the grand opening ceremony for the Cyber Foundry.Read More&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="navy-news-releases" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#navy-news-releases">
##
&lt;/a>
Navy News Releases
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4072087/commanding-officer-of-uss-harry-s-truman-relieved/">Commanding Officer of USS Harry S. Truman Relieved&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4071603/chief-of-naval-operations-visits-new-england-bases-stresses-lethality-and-readi/">Chief of Naval Operations Visits New England Bases, Stresses Lethality and Readiness&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4065786/uss-harry-s-truman-involved-in-collision-at-sea/">USS Harry S. Truman Involved in Collision at Sea&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4063597/chief-of-naval-operations-visits-nswc-crane-purdue-university/">Chief of Naval Operations Visits NSWC Crane, Purdue University&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4059675/us-navy-leaders-observe-joint-task-force-southern-guard-operations/">U.S. Navy Leaders Observe Joint Task Force Southern Guard Operations&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4056366/truman-strike-group-units-arrive-in-greece-for-port-visit/">Truman Strike Group Units Arrive in Greece for Port Visit&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4055192/chief-of-naval-operations-hosts-thailands-head-of-navy-for-counterpart-visit/">Chief of Naval Operations Hosts Thailand’s Head of Navy for Counterpart Visit&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4054043/chief-of-naval-operations-adm-lisa-franchetti-met-with-commander-in-chief-of-th/">Chief of Naval Operations Adm. Lisa Franchetti met with Commander-in-Chief of the Royal Thai Navy (RTN) Adm. Jirapol Wongwit, at the Pentagon, Feb. 4, 2025.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4044322/operation-southern-spear-latest-development-in-operationalizing-robotic-and-aut/">Operation Southern Spear: Latest Development in Operationalizing Robotic and Autonomous Systems&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.navy.mil/Press-Office/Press-Releases/display-pressreleases/Article/4041783/us-navy-installations-fleet-commands-participate-in-annual-force-protection-exe/">U.S. Navy Installations, Fleet Commands Participate in Annual Force Protection Exercise&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="uscg-news-releases" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#uscg-news-releases">
##
&lt;/a>
USCG News Releases
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4086888/coast-guard-interdicts-21-aliens-west-of-point-loma-calif/">Coast Guard interdicts 21 aliens west of Point Loma, Calif.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4085805/coast-guard-medevacs-cruise-ship-passenger-experiencing-strokes-300-miles-offsh/">Coast Guard medevacs cruise ship passenger experiencing strokes 300 miles offshore Hawaii&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4084594/availability-of-public-notice-for-highway-bridge-proposal-over-petaluma-river/">Availability of Public Notice for highway bridge proposal over Petaluma River&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4084005/multimedia-release-coast-guard-port-of-virginia-maritime-incident-response-team/">MULTIMEDIA RELEASE: Coast Guard, Port of Virginia Maritime Incident Response Team conclude search and rescue forum in Hampton&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4080606/coast-guard-issues-captain-of-the-port-order-to-puerto-nuevo-terminal-for-viola/">Coast Guard issues Captain of the Port order to Puerto Nuevo Terminal for violating hazardous cargo handling permit in San Juan&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4078346/coast-guard-encounters-over-a-dozen-aliens-off-the-coast-of-southern-california/">Coast Guard encounters over a dozen aliens off the coast of southern California&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4077268/coast-guard-sector-miami-partners-stop-12-illegal-charters-2-violated-federal-o/">Coast Guard Sector Miami, partners stop 12 illegal charters, 2 violated federal orders&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4076442/media-availability-coast-guard-port-of-virginia-maritime-incident-response-team/">MEDIA AVAILABILITY: Coast Guard, Port of Virginia Maritime Incident Response Team to host search and rescue forum in Hampton, Va.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4076177/coast-guard-suspends-search-for-person-missing-near-the-entrance-to-the-ambrose/">Coast Guard suspends search for person missing near the entrance to the Ambrose Channel&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.news.uscg.mil/Press-Releases/Article/4075625/update-coast-guard-continues-search-for-one-person-after-five-recovered-from-si/">UPDATE: Coast Guard continues search for one person after five recovered from sinking boat near the entrance to the Ambrose Channel&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="space-force-news" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#space-force-news">
##
&lt;/a>
Space Force News
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4086496/dod-releases-guidance-for-dod-civilian-employees-on-responding-to-opms-what-you/">DoD releases guidance for DoD civilian employees on responding to OPM&amp;rsquo;s ‘What You Did Last Week’ email&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4086464/the-department-of-the-air-force-implements-deferred-resignation-program/">The Department of the Air Force implements Deferred Resignation Program&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4073073/hegseth-addresses-strengthening-military-by-cutting-excess-refocusing-dod-budget/">Hegseth addresses strengthening military by cutting excess, refocusing DOD budget&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4072069/deep-space-advanced-radar-capability-makes-tremendous-progress-in-first-year/">Deep Space Advanced Radar Capability makes tremendous progress in first year&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4071070/space-force-announces-2024-polaris-award-service-level-recipients/">Space Force announces 2024 Polaris Award service-level recipients&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4070872/minuteman-iii-test-launch-showcases-readiness-of-us-nuclear-forces-safe-effecti/">Minuteman III test launch showcases readiness of US nuclear force’s safe, effective deterrent&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4068983/cso-cmssf-represent-space-force-at-daytona-500/">CSO, CMSSF represent Space Force at Daytona 500&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4067768/space-force-leaders-visit-japan-to-strengthen-partnership/">Space Force leaders visit Japan to strengthen partnership&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4065182/daf-releases-memorandum-dei-and-gender-ideology-awards-guidance/">DAF releases memorandum DEI and Gender Ideology Awards Guidance&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.spaceforce.mil/News/Article-Display/Article/4065192/the-department-of-the-air-force-releases-memorandum-dei-and-gender-ideology-pub/">The Department of the Air Force releases memorandum DEI and Gender Ideology Publication Review&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details>
&lt;h1 id="cybercom-media-news" >
&lt;div>
&lt;a href="#cybercom-media-news">
##
&lt;/a>
Cybercom Media News
&lt;/div>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;details>
&lt;summary>View Articles&lt;/summary>
&lt;br>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3976294/us-cyber-command-deputy-commander-highlights-collaboration-innovation-at-uw-mad/">U.S. Cyber Command Deputy Commander Highlights Collaboration, Innovation at UW-Madison Tech Talk&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3966564/media-release-uscybercom-executes-international-coordinated-cyber-security-acti/">Media Release: USCYBERCOM Executes International Coordinated Cyber Security Activity 2024&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3905064/uscybercom-unveils-ai-roadmap-for-cyber-operations/">USCYBERCOM Unveils AI Roadmap for Cyber Operations&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3893166/us-cyber-command-hosts-first-offensive-cyber-flag-2024-exercise/">U.S. Cyber Command Hosts First Offensive Cyber Flag 2024 Exercise&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3895345/russian-disinformation-campaign-doppelgnger-unmasked-a-web-of-deception/">Russian Disinformation Campaign “DoppelGänger” Unmasked: A Web of Deception&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3905062/7-cs-infrastructure-team-completes-base-network-upgrade/">7 CS infrastructure team completes base network upgrade&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3783991/cnmf-deploys-first-defensive-cyber-team-to-zambia/">CNMF deploys first defensive cyber team to Zambia&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3782423/us-cyber-command-darpa-advance-partnership-with-new-agreement/">U.S. Cyber Command, DARPA Advance Partnership with New Agreement&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/4051492/morgan-m-adamski-appointed-as-next-executive-director-of-uscybercom/">Morgan M. Adamski Appointed as Next Executive Director of USCYBERCOM&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://12ft.io/https://www.cybercom.mil/Media/News/Article/3754641/cyber-recon-2024-recognizes-excellence-fosters-collaboration/">Cyber Recon 2024 Recognizes Excellence, Fosters Collaboration&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/details></description></item></channel></rss>